<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Mapplas</string>
    <string name="location_error">Location system error</string>
    <string name="location_needed">Location service is needed to work properly</string>
    <string name="unknown_error">Unknown error</string>
    <string name="title">Title</string>
    <string name="app_detail">App Detail</string>
    <string name="web">web</string>
    <string name="email">Email</string>
    <string name="description">Description</string>
    <string name="location_searching">Getting your location!</string>
    <string name="location_done">Location retrived correctly</string>
    <string name="rating_rate">Rate App</string>
    <string name="accept">Accept</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="send">Send</string>
    <string name="rate">rate</string>
    <string name="category">Cathegory</string>
    <string name="pin_ups">pins</string>
    <string name="getting_configuration">Loading configuration&#8230;</string>
    <string name="pin_up">pin</string>
    <string name="un_pin_up">unpin</string>
    <string name="share">share</string>
    <string name="block">block</string>
    <string name="ptr_pull_to_refresh">Pull to refresh&#8230;</string>
    <string name="ptr_release_to_refresh">Release to refresh&#8230;</string>
    <string name="ptr_refreshing">Loading Apps&#8230;</string>
    <string name="unable_geoloc">Ups, we can\'t get your position!!!</string>
    <string name="block_title">Block App</string>
    <string name="block_text">You are going to block this app. Are you sure?</string>
    <string name="block_accept">Block it!</string>
    <string name="block_cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="developer">More from developer</string>
    <string name="devMail">Developer Mail</string>
    <string name="devWeb">Developer Web</string>
    <string name="blocks">blocks</string>
    <string name="yes">Yes</string>
    <string name="no">No</string>
    <string name="allow">allow</string>
    <string name="done">Done</string>
    <string name="free">Free</string>
    <string name="wifi_error_toast">Improve the search! For more accurate recommendations, turn Wi-Fi on. This works even when not connected to a network.</string>
    <string name="pull_to_refresh_wifi_error">Turn Wi-Fi on to improve your recommendations!</string>
    <string name="location_error_toast">Your location cannot be found. Please try again later.</string>
    <string name="menu_refresh">Refresh</string>
    <string name="image_content_description">content description</string>
    <string name="profile_empty_pinup_list">You don\'t have any pinned up apps</string>
    <string name="profile_empty_block_list">You don\'t have any blocked apps</string>
    <string name="descriptive_geoloc_error">Oops\! It seems that you\'re in Wonderland.</string>
    <string name="menu_config">About us</string>
    <string name="preferences_title">About us</string>
    <string name="terms_of_use_title">Terms of use</string>
    <string name="terms_of_use_message"><![CDATA[<p><strong>Terms of Services</strong></p><p>Mapplas is operated by Mapplas Innovations SL, a company registered in Spain under the following reference: CIF number B75081935. Mapplas provides its service to you subject to the following Terms of Use (\'Terms\'), which we may update from time to time without notice. By visiting our website www.mapplas.com (or any other URL provided further in our Terms) or using our service, you automatically agree to be bound by the Terms as set out below,even if you have not explicitly consented to this by clicking on \'I agree\' or a similar online consent mechanism.</p><p><strong>Changes to Mapplas.com and terms of use</strong></p><p>We reserve the right to modify or terminate the Mapplas.com service for any reason, and without notice, without liability to you or any third party. We also reserve the right to modify these Terms of Service from time to time without notice. You are responsible for regularly reviewing these Terms of Service to check for possible changes.</p><p><strong>Registration obligations</strong></p><p>You must download and activate Mapplas software in order to access the Service. By doing so, you will provide true, accurate, and complete information, and maintain and promptly update this information. If you provide any information that is untrue, inaccurate, or incomplete, or Mapplas has reasonable grounds to suspect that the information is untrue, inaccurate, or incomplete, Mapplas has the right to suspend or terminate your membership and access to the Service. You are responsible for obtaining access to the Service, which access may involve third party fees (such as Internet service provider charges). In addition, you must provide and are responsible for all equipment necessary to access the Service.<br/></p><p><strong>Mapplas Description of Service</strong></p><p>Mapplas is a service that aims to<br/><br/>facilitate one-to-one and one-to-many exchange of preferred or selected apps, referenced by links, also facilitating download and installation by thereceiving end-users.<br/>provide recommendations and discovery tools for applications.<br/></p><p><strong>PRIVACY POLICY</strong></p><p>The service including the software Mapplas provides (including, but not limited to tracking software and online sharing service) is made available to you for your personal, non-commercial use only (at home or at work). Mapplas may from time to time use OpenUDID, UDID or your IP address to measure download rates between a sponsored link and an effective download. We may also use this information to authenticate a session.</p><p>In addition you may not modify, adapt, translate, or reverse engineer any portion of the Mapplas service nor remove any copyright, trademark or other proprietary rights notices contained in or on the Mapplas service or use any robot, spider, site search/retrieval application, or other device to retrieve or index any portion of the Mapplas service. You may not reformat or frame any portion of the web pages that are part of the Mapplas service or create or transmit unwanted electronic communications such as \'pam,\' or chain letters to third parties.</p><p>Furthermore, you may not use Mapplas in any manner that could damage, disable, overburden, or impair Mapplas\'s services (e.g., you may not use Mapplas in an automated manner to create spam), nor may you use Mapplas in any manner that could interfere with any other party\'s use and enjoyment of Mapplas\'s services. You may not use any 3rd party toolbars or scripts to access Mapplas.</p><p>You may not use the Mapplas service for any illegal or unauthorized purpose. International users agree to comply with all local rules regarding online conduct and acceptable content. You are solely responsible for your conduct and any data, text, information, graphics, photos, profiles, audio and video clips, links and other content (\'Materials\') that you add, submit, post, and display on the Mapplas.com service. You grant us a non-exclusive non-revocable license to use the Materials for the sake of the Mapplas service. Because Mapplas merely serves as a repository of information, user-posted Materials do not represent the advice, views, opinions or beliefs of Mapplas, and Mapplas makes no claim of accuracy of any user-posted Materials.</p><p>Multiple Mapplas accounts held by the same individual are subject to termination unless expressly authorized by Mapplas. We also reserve the right, but shall have no obligation, to remove Materials that we determine in our sole discretion are unlawful, fraudulent, threatening, libelous, defamatory, obscene or otherwise objectionable, or infringes or violates any party\'s intellectual property or other proprietary rights or these Terms of Use. Any account posting objectionable content is subject to termination. We reserve the right to disable (some of) the functionalities (e.g. transferability of links) of the Mapplas service for any account at any time, without notice, without liability to you or any third party.</p><p>Accounts created with the primary intention to promote a product or service are considered SPAM and are subject to termination unless expressly authorized by Mapplas. We reserve the right to remove content that we determine in our sole discretion is primarily intended to promote a product or service.</p><p>We reserve the right, to limit the amount of Materials that you can add to the Mapplas service.</p><p>If you have comments on Mapplas and its service, or ideas on how to improve it, please contact us support@mapplas.com. Please note that by doing so, you also grant Mapplas the right to use and incorporate your ideas or comments into Mapplas\'s software, service or website without further compensation. If you do not agree to this policy then please do not send us your ideas, comments and suggestions, by email or otherwise.</p><p><strong>Mapplas\'s proprietary rights</strong></p><p>Mapplas\'s policy is to prohibit children under the age of 13 from accessing, registering, or using any of Mapplas\'s products and services. You may not register or use the Service if you are under 13 years old. By registering, installing, and accepting these Terms you represent to Mapplas that you are at least 13 years old.</p><p><strong>PRIVACY POLICY</strong></p><p>Certain registration information and other information about you may be collected by Mapplas and through the Service. Mapplas\'s use of this information is governed by the Mapplas Privacy Policy</p><p><strong>Mapplas\'s proprietary rights</strong></p><p>By submitting, posting or displaying any Materials on or through the Mapplas service, you automatically grant to us a worldwide, non-exclusive, sublicenseable, transferable, royalty-free, perpetual, irrevocable right to copy, distribute, create derivative works of, publicly perform and display such Materials. If Materials you own are deleted from the Mapplas service, these rights are revoked.</p><p>You acknowledge that Mapplas owns all right, title and interest in and to the Mapplas website and service, including without limitation all Intellectual Property Rights. \'Intellectual Property Rights\' means any and all rights existing from time to time under patent law, copyright law, trade secret law, trademark law, unfair competition law, and any and all other proprietary rights, and any and all applications, renewals, extensions and restorations thereof, now or hereafter in force and effect worldwide. Except as expressly authorized (in written permission) by Mapplas, you may not copy, modify, publish, license, create derivative works, reverse engineer, transmit, distribute, perform, display or sell any of Mapplas\'s proprietary information or software.</p><p><strong>Delete account</strong></p><p>You have the right to delete your account anytime you want. To delete your account, please send us an email to support@Mapplas.com specifying that you want to delete your account. A person from Mapplas will contact you to confirm, and your account will be deleted within a few days.</p><p><strong>Privacy for Children</strong></p><p>Mapplas does not knowingly collect any information about children under the age of 13, and we delete all personal information for that person if/when it occurs. If you are aware of anyone under the age of 13 whose personal information may have been given to Mapplas, we will make every effort to ensure that whatever information we have is permanently purged from our records.</p><p><strong>MODIFICATIONS TO SERVICE</strong></p><p>Mapplas reserves the right at any time to modify or discontinue, temporarily or permanently, the Service or any part of it with or without notice. Mapplas will not be liable to you or to any third party for any modification, suspension, or discontinuance of the Service.</p><p>Disclaimer of warranties</p><p>Mapplas disclaims any and all responsibility or liability for the accuracy, content, completeness, legality, reliability, or operability or availability of information or materials displayed on the Mapplas service and website. Mapplas disclaims any and all responsibility and liability for the conduct of third parties on the website.</p><p>Mapplas SOFTWARE AND WEBSITE IS PROVIDED \'AS IS,\' WITH NO WARRANTIES WHATSOEVER. Mapplas DISCLAIMS ANY WARRANTIES REGARDING THE SECURITY, RELIABILITY, TIMELINESS, AND PERFORMANCE OF THE Mapplas SOFTWARE AND WEBSITE.</p><p>YOU UNDERSTAND AND AGREE THAT YOU DOWNLOAD AND/OR USE THE Mapplas SOFTWARE AND SERVICES AT YOUR OWN DISCRETION AND RISK AND THAT YOU WILL BE SOLELY RESPONSIBLE FOR ANY DAMAGES TO YOUR COMPUTER SYSTEM OR LOSS OF DATA THAT RESULTS FROM THE DOWNLOAD OR USE OF Mapplas SOFTWARE.</p><p>UNDER NO CIRCUMSTANCES SHALL MAPPLAS BE LIABLE TO ANY USER ON ACCOUNT OF THAT USER\'S USE OR MISUSE OF THE MAPPLAS SERVICE AND WEBSITE. SUCH LIMITATION OF LIABILITY SHALL APPLY TO PREVENT RECOVERY OF DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, CONSEQUENTIAL, SPECIAL, EXEMPLARY, AND PUNITIVE DAMAGES WHETHER SUCH CLAIM IS BASED ON WARRANTY, CONTRACT, TORT (INCLUDING NEGLIGENCE), OR OTHERWISE, (EVEN IF MAPPLAS HAS BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES). SUCH LIMITATION OF LIABILITY SHALL APPLY WHETHER THE DAMAGES ARISE FROM USE OR MISUSE OF AND RELIANCE ON THE MAPPLAS SERVICES AND WEBSITE, FROM INABILITY TO USE THE MAPPLAS SERVICES AND WEBSITE, OR FROM THE INTERRUPTION, SUSPENSION, OR TERMINATION OF THE MAPPLAS SERVICES AND WEBSITE (INCLUDING SUCH DAMAGES INCURRED BY THIRD PARTIES). SUCH LIMITATION SHALL APPLY NOTWITHSTANDING A FAILURE OF ESSENTIAL PURPOSE OF ANY LIMITED REMEDY AND TO THE FULLEST EXTENT PERMITTED BY LAW. YOUR ONLY RIGHT WITH RESPECT TO ANY DISSATISFACTION WITH THE MAPPLAS SERVICES AND WEBSITE SHALL BE TO TERMINATE USE OF THE Mapplas SERVICES AND WEBSITE. SOME COUNTRIES DO NOT ALLOW THE EXCLUSION OR LIMITATION OF DAMAGES IN WHICH CASE ANY LIABILITY FOR DAMAGES AND COST SHALL BE LIMITED TO EURO 1.000,-. </p><p>WHILE MAPPLAS STRIVES TO MIRROR THE PRICES OF APPS AS THEY ARE LISTED IN APPLE\'S APP STORE, FROM TIME TO TIME THERE MAY BE BRIEF DISCREPANCIES BETWEEN THE LISTED PRICE OF AN APP IN THE APP STORE AND THE PRICE DISPLAYED IN MAPPLAS. MAPPLAS IS NOT LIABLE FOR ANY PURCHASES MADE IN THE APP STORE FOR APPS DISCOVERED THROUGH MAPPLAS SERVICES.</p><p>In view of the fact that Mapplas is offering its service free of charge, you agree that abovementioned full exclusion of liability and full disclaimer of any and all warranties is fair and acceptable to you.</p>]]></string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_title">Privacy policy</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_message"><![CDATA[<p><strong>Privacy Policy</strong></p><p>Your privacy is very important to us. By using Mapplas, you agree to our privacy as described below.</p><p><strong>What you should know</strong></p><p>Read below to to get an overview of what our service entails. If you have any concerns that aren\'t covered here, please contact us at (support [at] mapplas [dot] com).</p><p>We will never sell, lease, or share your private information with anyone, with or without personally identifying information. We may sell, lease, or share information about user behavior in aggregate manner only. For example, we may conduct a study to find the most shared apps in the Games category across our entire platform.</p><p>You can delete apps from your profile at any time. You can also delete your account at any time.</p><p>We don\'t spam and never will. We may from time to time send updates about important Mapplas news. We may also offer email opt-in services for notifications purposes.</p><p>Other users can\'t see any of your data or personal information, unless you choose to let them. In the future Mapplas may introduce more features that will allow you to more easily control what data is shared and what remains fully private.</p><p>We use the data collected in your app collection to serve affiliate links that point to Apple\'s App Store.</p><p>Mapplas serves promoted recommendations that are paid by certain advertisers. Promoted recommendations are marked as such.</p><p>We use Google Analytics to measure the traffic on our site and this comes in form of aggregate data. More info is provided by Google on their privacy policy here http://www.google.com/intl/en_ALL/privacy.</p><p>We use analytics services to measure how our iOS, Android and Windows Phone apps are used. Those services do not provide any identifiable information about you and enable us to improve the service.</p><p><strong>What information does Mapplas collect?</strong></p><p>Mapplas typically does not collect any data beyond the cookie (see section below) on it\'s web properties not involving an explicit login with Mapplas (direct login or via Facebook Connect).</p><p>Once you activate an Mapplas profile on your desktop or mobile device, we create a personal, private account. Mapplas collects some information from your account in order to provide you and other users with recommendations and promotional services. Account information on a given user may include elements of the following list that may evolve over time: IP address, an email, a list of applications (owned or favorited), an OpenUDID, UDID, and preference settings for that user.</p><p>Mapplas may use the information mentioned above in order to improve its service. For example, we may aggregate this data in an anonymous way to analyze how many users are sharing apps in a particular category.</p><p>This information is stored safely and securely.</p><p><strong>How we use cookies and log files</strong></p><p>Mapplas may create a \'cookie\' in your browser containing an identification number that is unique to the computer you are using. We may use this cookie to provide you with a smooth experience.</p><p>Logs are used to record how our site/service is being used. As with most websites, we log each visit to each web page. A log entry can contain information typically found in the \'header\' of your web browser\'s request such as the browser type you used, your internet protocol address, and the date and time of day. We may also log your cookie\'s identification number and the URL of the last site you visited. This log information is important for security, audit, and quality improvement, as well as for monitoring the health of our service. </p>]]></string>
    <string name="currency_euro">€</string>
    <string name="currency_dollar">$</string>
    <string name="share_message_part1">Sharing</string>
    <string name="share_message_part2"> via Mapplas</string>
    <string name="conf_screen_contact_title">Contact us</string>
    <string name="config_contact_us_email">support@mapplas.com</string>
    <string name="config_contact_us_email_subject">Hello!</string>
    <string name="app_detail_app_web_dev_url_error">Error loading web page. Try again.</string>
    <string name="error">error</string>
    <string name="user_screen_segmented_control_blocks">Blocked</string>
    <string name="user_screen_segmented_control_pins">Pinned</string>
    <string name="comming_soon_title">Mapplas shows great apps around you.</string>
    <string name="comming_soon_subtitle">Or your country is not currently supported or something went wrong.</string>
    <string name="comming_soon_pull">Pull to refresh</string>
    <string name="problem_launching_app">Sorry, there is a problem launching the app.</string>
    <string name="language_change_list_item">Language:</string>
    <string name="language_change_alert_title">Choose language</string>
    <string name="language_english">English</string>
    <string name="language_spanish">Castellano</string>
    <string name="language_basque">Euskera</string>
    <string name="language_change_restart_app_message">An application restart is needed after language change</string>
    <string name="connection_error">It seems there\'s no connection. Enable it and try again.</string>
	<string name="connection_switch_error">Internet connection problem. Try again please.</string>
    <string name="google_positioning_alert_dialog_title">Location services disabled</string>
    <string name="google_positioning_alert_dialog_message">Mapplas needs access to your location. Please turn on Location Services.</string>
    <string name="google_positioning_alert_dialog_enable">Enable</string>
    <string name="comming_soon_notify_user">Notify me when available</string>
    <string name="notify_user_dialog_title">Receive an email</string>
    <string name="notify_user_dialog_message">Insert your email and we will notify you when mapplas is available in your country</string>
</resources>